export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is the sum of the first 10 positive whole numbers?",
      option1: "55",
      option2: "62",
      option3: "58",
      option4: "61",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the longest side of a right triangle called?",
      option1: "adjacent",
      option2: "side",
      option3: "leg",
      option4: "hypotenuse",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the number that is a 1 followed by 100 zeros?",
      option1: "googol",
      option2: "zillion",
      option3: "gagillion",
      option4: "moogol",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the mathematical constant that appears in circles?",
      option1: "radius",
      option2: "360 degrees",
      option3: "pi",
      option4: "inscribed angle",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is one way to describe the slope of a line?",
      option1: "find y-intercept",
      option2: "rise over run",
      option3: "count the climb from down to up",
      option4: "count the climb from left to right",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the highest common factor of 30 and 132?",
      option1: "3",
      option2: "10",
      option3: "6",
      option4: "4",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of sin of 90 degrees?",
      option1: "(square root of 2) over 2",
      option2: "3/4",
      option3: "1/2",
      option4: "1",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "When two circles have the same centre, what is it called?",
      option1: "Similar Circles",
      option2: "Concentric Circles",
      option3: "Identical Circles",
      option4: "Equivalent Circles",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "When something is going to occur, which mathematical term is used to express the likelihood of the event?",
      option1: "Likelihood",
      option2: "Probability",
      option3: "Certain",
      option4: "Percentage",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "123+4-5+67-89?",
      option1: "100",
      option2: "110",
      option3: "90",
      option4: "109",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many vertices are present in a cube?",
      option1: "10",
      option2: "9",
      option3: "6",
      option4: "8",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "An object is thrown into the air. After a while, it falls back to the Earth. The flight path of the object traces what shape?",
      option1: "exponential curve",
      option2: "abosolute value graph",
      option3: "parabola",
      option4: "linear graph",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How many hours are there in a year (rounded to the nearest hour)?",
      option1: "8760",
      option2: "9740",
      option3: "7530",
      option4: "8570",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A man is currently 4 times older than his son. In 10 years, the man will be three times older than his son. What is the manâ€™s age presently?",
      option1: "90",
      option2: "100",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "80",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which prime number is closest to 100?",
      option1: "201",
      option2: "101",
      option3: "120",
      option4: "111",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What graph represents categorical data instead of numerical?",
      option1: "histogram",
      option2: "stem and leaf plot",
      option3: "box plot",
      option4: "bar graph",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "6 to the power of zero is?",
      option1: "6",
      option2: "0",
      option3: "1",
      option4: "3",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "If a number is divisible by 9, the sum of its digits is divisible by?",
      option1: "3",
      option2: "6",
      option3: "9",
      option4: "1",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "If a triangle is rotated around the y axis what 3D shape is formed?",
      option1: "cone",
      option2: "circle",
      option3: "pyramid",
      option4: "rectangular prism",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "If a ball is thrown in the air and it's path is represented by a parabola with a starting point at 0 and a vertex at 6 seconds, how long was the ball in th air before it hit the ground?",
      option1: "6",
      option2: "12",
      option3: "3",
      option4: "18",
      ans: 2,
    },
  ];